FROM ME TO YOU
WORKING TOGETHER
Sawako!
I got it!
Sawako, hi!
- Do your best!
- I will.
And so, if the ball gets passed here,
Sawako, you need to make your move...
- quickly, like this.
- I see. Uh-huh.
Listen, this is big. Obviously, the
opponent's gonna get in your way. But
don't panic just pass the
ball back to your team.
It's important to visualize the flow of
the game and try to predict what's coming
next. -It's actually like playing
soccer in your head! -She's really
excited.
Makes sense, though, 'cause
field day's coming up soon.
Sawako!
- Hm?
You lower your hips down, kinda like
this. Then, you take the inner side of
your foot and try to gouge the ball
precisely and with all your might...
...you push it out! Push it out!
Push it out! Push it out! Push it out!
- I get it. -Push it out! Once more...
- Sawako!
See ya!
Bye-bye.
- What?
- I made friends with her.
No way!
- Come on! She for real?!
- Well, I think it's fairly obvious
that you don't like her very much.
How can you tell, Yano-chin?
Cause you're simple.
Well, I mean it's good that
Sadako's making more friends, but...
Really? Friends?
Bye-bye... Bye-bye... Bye-bye...
What if she ends up closer to her
than us, I'll honestly be so pissed off!
Aw, you're adorable,
you know that, Chizu?
Another one. I can't believe
I made another new friend.
To be honest, I didn't exactly work
for it, so it hasn't really sunk in.
Yeah, we're friends... I mean,
obviously we are, aren't we?
I'm new to this, but I wonder if making
new friends... is supposed to feel like
this?
I haven't had much time to process
it but I know it makes me happy.
Ku-ro-numa!
W- Why did... Kazehaya's face just pop up?!
He had nothing to do with what I was just
thinking about! I can't fall asleep now!
I still can't believe Kurumi chose to
be my friend. I've been so lucky lately...
Though the universe has been
finding a way to balance it out.
Here.
Th- Thanks for that.
Uh, yeah.
- What's the deal with those two?
- Can't tell? They're
- self-conscious. Full of nerves.
- Hmm?
Th- This is a problem.
For some reason... I can't seem to have a
normal conversation with Kazehaya anymore.
Kazehaya!
What's up?
It's the committee's handout. I
was asked to deliver it to you. Here.
Oh, thanks! Oh yeah,
the CD! Wait here a sec.
You brought it for me? Thank you!
Let's see... here it is!
- Here you go.
- Yay! Awesome!
So natural!
She's super cute, and a
good person, and friendly.
Kurumi really is in a tier of her own.
Thanks for everything.
I bet she would never have
awkward encounters like that.
She just kinda... has this
natural way about her. Must be nice...
Sawako! Is something wrong?
- Woah, thank you.
- Mm-mm. It's my bad for startling you.
I called you, but I
guess you didn't hear me.
I'm sorry I should have
been paying better attention.
Here you are.
Thanks so much, So, uh, I, uh...
Ku...
K- Kurumi.
I- I called her by her
name. Or was that too friendly?
That's the first time you've
called me by name directly. Awesome!
I made the right choice!
- That's heavy right? Want me to hold half?
- No, I'm fine. This is my
mission and mine alone!
Your "mission?" You're so funny, Sawako!
Seriously. It would be so nice
if I could become more like her.
Kazehaya! I got you the
handout! Lend me your CD, will ya?
Okay!
- Nice! Thank you!
- Yay!
- M-Maybe that's too far.
- Sawako?
Hey, Is there something
that's been bothering you lately?
Cause If there is, know you can always
talk to me! If you're comfortable telling
- me, I'll listen!
- Not really "bothering" me...
Well, you can tell me anything!
Seriously? My role model... is
offering to give me advice?
- I'm ready! Bring it on!
- Pitch to contact! Let's go!
- You can't talk naturally with Kazehaya?
- Yes, Maybe it's just "different"
chatting with boys than it is with girls?
- You're thinking about it too hard!
- I knew it!
Let me tell you something, coming from
someone who's known Kazehaya super well
since middle school...
Yes? As long as I've known him, he's
never been able to leave outcasts alone.
He talks to anyone and I mean everyone,
naturally, Even you're no exception,
Sawako So, I'm sure he
would talk to you the same way.
Yeah! You're right! That's true!
So yeah. The way that he's been talking
to you isn't really anything out of the
ordinary or special. -I don't think you
need to drive yourself so crazy over it.
I see!
Ah! But you should consider that you
and Kazehaya are very different types of
- people too.
- Uh-huh.
So when you think about it, even if it's
another boy, rather than a cheerful person
like Kazehaya... ...you might find it easier
to talk to someone who's a little more
like you, you know?
When it comes down to it, each person
has their own place where they belong in
- society.
- Ah, you're teaching me so much.
So, that must be why it seems so natural
whenever I see you and Kazehaya talk to
- each other.
- You think so?
Well, Kazehaya and I do share a
lot of similar qualities, you know...
Wow!
Now that I think about it, whenever he
talks to her, he uses her first name,
doesn't he?
You seem kinda close... to each other.
I wouldn't really say close. We're normal!
Wha-? That's normal?
I didn't know the standard for
"normal" was so high! Amazing!
I'm learning so much. I mean, if that's
what's normal for someone like you, it'd
- make sense that I'd be nervous.
- Well, we should start heading back.
Y- Yeah.
Hey there, Kuronuma!
In the beginning I
couldn't even greet him properly.
That used to be my "normal," didn't it?
Then it's fine.
Um, Kurumi?
I think after talking about all of this
with you, I'm feeling much more positive.
Thank you so much!
I'll think of it as one step at a time!
Sure, I'll still be nervous... but I'm gonna
- push myself!
- Wait...
Later!
- Sawako!
- So, uh, you think if I keep working at
it, I could become more like you one day?
I-I'm getting ahead of myself, no way I
could do that. I'm sorry, please forget
what I just said!
Kurumi is like... hmm, how do I put this?
Well, this is from when we
were in middle school, but still...
Chizu.
Hm?
Yumi told me that she
really likes Kazehaya.
And well... since you are so close with
him, think maybe you could help her out a
- little?
- I don't exactly "hate" when
someone depends on me for something, so...
Gotcha~ you just need me to make an
opening for them to be alone together,
- right? That's a piece of cake!
- I knew we were right to trust you, Chizu!
So after that. She took the chance
and asked him out, but she was rejected.
Ah. And, up to that
point, it wasn't so bad...
Chizu, please help her too?
Huh?
- Chizu, will you help her now?
- Uh...
Chizu, help me too!
Chizu, me next!
Hey, Kazehaya So... there's another
girl who wants to talk to you, so...
Seriously? Again?
No! I'm done!
- What? But Why?!
So you'll go and help Yumi,
but I'm not worth the effort?!
You're taking her
side, aren't you, Chizu?!
- W-What a pain in the butt.
- Hey, Chizu, how come? Why?
Wait!
Chizu didn't do anything wrong! This is
wrong. The girls in our class shouldn't be
fighting like this!
That's why if it's come to this...
...It's better if nobody ever asks him out!
I seriously couldn't care less.
- You're so right!
- Kazehaya belongs to everyone!
I can't stress enough how little I care.
In the end, the girls were scared of
Kazehaya being taken by someone so they
decided it'd be better to unite.
Hmm, How do I explain it? If you were to
ask I wouldn't say she's a bad person. But
I kinda felt forced to help, y'know...
And I hate it! It's awful! 'So,
yeah I want nothing to do with her!
So, you were taken advantage of, huh?
Hearing your story gave me a clear image
of just the sort of girl Kurumi is. Now
then, let's see if things go according
to her plan or if she's met her match.
Got it!
- How 'bout we take a little break guys?
- Yeah!
I'll be right back. I'm
gonna go buy something to drink.
Oh, while you're at it,
can you grab me some tea?
Sure thing!
Do you think you think if I keep working
at it, I could become more like you one
day?
I'm pretty sure I sounded
completely ridiculous. How embarrassing.
Kuronuma?
K-Kazehaya?
Uh... aw man... I'm the one who called
out to you, but I'm getting nervous.
Wait. Kazehaya's nervous?
It's just... we haven't
chatted much recently.
Ah, what am I even saying?
I, I headed this way 'cause I was going
to buy some drinks, and I just happened to
- see you... that's all!
- I see... This whole time,
Kazehaya was nervous too.
Well...
So that must mean... that he's been
worrying over the same things that I have.
That's the first since Ryu's house.
Kazehaya...
- You smiled.
It's been a while since I saw you smile.
I'm so glad.
Oh yeah, Maru's gotten pretty big.
- Like, about this size.
- Wow!
He's a total rascal, he runs around the
house destroying things like a hurricane.
Mm-hm! It's about time
we build him a doghouse.
Aw, Maru...
You should come visit.
But when I think about it, Maru does seem
to get really lonely! So I don't know if
he'll stay put even if we
do build him a doghouse.
Sawako, hey!
Kurumizawa!
"Zawa?"
- Kurumizawa... zawa?
- Zawa, zawa... zawa, zawa... zawa, zawa...
you didn't know? Her
full name's Ume Kurumizawa.
So Ume is her... first name?
- Yeah. Isn't that right?
- Uh- huh.
So that's what I should call her.
Yeah, Kurumizawa.
So, then this whole time... he
wasn't calling her by her first name.
Ume Kurumizawa. Her first name's Ume.
Huh? I think I feel relieved.
Ka...
Kazehaya, is it cool if I
borrow Sawako for a second?
Uh, sure, I guess.
It has to be just us
since it's a girl talk.
Did she say a girl talk?
It's always something. Why do
I keep getting interrupted?
So, it's a girl talk. I wonder
what she wants to talk to me about.
How far are we going to walk though?
Hey, uh, Kuru...
Hey, Ume?
Don't call me "Ume!"
Kurumi... Just call me that!
Oh, you got it.
I see, it's her nickname.
For a second, I thought she was
upset with me for being too friendly.
To tell you the truth,
there's someone that I like.
I want him to be my boyfriend, but I'm
not confident enough to take the next step
and I was wondering what I should do.
What would you do in this situation?
W- What you should do? I
dunno, what SHOULD you do?!
She's depending on me, Ah,
but nothing's coming to mind!
No, it's... It's just that I'd
like you to help me out, Sawako.
Me? Kurumi's asking for my help?
Are you sure you want that?
I just asked you specifically.
I want it to be you, Sawako!
I don't think... I've ever been relied
on like this before. This is huge!
- I'll do my best!
- You'll help me? Thank you!
But I have no idea
what I'm supposed to do.
I'll tell you what to do, so
don't worry about that part.
... but if I get involved in your love
life, you sure I won't end up ruining the
- mood or something like that?
- It'll be fine. After all,
it's someone you know well.
Kazehaya.
The person I like... it's Kazehaya.
It's... Kazehaya?
My heart wavers.
This incomparable feeling.
Next time: "Special?"